我不確定哪個聞著更惡心
I'm not sure what smells worse,
水還是垃圾
the water or the trash.
目前而言 我覺得最惡心的是我們
At this point, I'd say it's us.
我是怎麼被你套路來這兒的
How did I let you talk me into this?
要怪就怪耶魯
Blame Yale.
是他們認為
They're the ones who find applicants
做過社區服務的申請人更受歡迎
with community service hours to be highly desirable.
難以置信 我能通玩水球和曲棍球
Unbelievable. I'm all-state in water polo and lacrosse,
我的祖先乘坐五月花號來到這裏
and my ancestors came over on the Mayflower.
沒有比這更全面的了
It doesn't get more well-rounded than that.
那是什麼
What is that?
-一只靴子 -怎麼會有人丟只靴子
- A boot? - How does somebody lose a boot?
要弄髒了
That's gonna stain.
哦 去你的吧
Oh, screw this.
耶魯可以把我列到等候名單裏了
Yale can wait-list me.
♪ NCIS 16x08 ♪ Friendly Fire
翻譯：湯湯 柒九一九 二噁英 小飛
校對： 二噁英 小飛
主校：Vincent
分配：雞血
== sync, corrected by elderman == @elder_man
太酷了 謝謝
That's so cool. Thank you.
哈 看看是誰終於到了
Ah, look who finally made it.
你們倆去哪了
Where have the two of you been?
另一次日出速寫集會
Oh, another sunrise sketching session.
你們見過海軍大院裏的黎明嗎
Have you guys ever taken in dawn at the, uh, Navy Yard?
十分靜謐
It is quite peaceful.
-這周第五次集會了 -沒錯 那起街頭藝術的案子
- That's the fifth time this week. - Yeah, that street art case
激勵我們回到繪畫上
really inspired us to get back into drawing.
你們倆扮畢加索的時候
So while the two of you have been playing Picasso,
McGee和我忙得累死累活
McGee and I have been working our asses off.
哦 是嗎
Oh, really?
哈 我很確定你鑽研這個是非常用心的
Ha! Diligent research, I'm sure. Hmm.
好了 讓我看看你們畫了什麼
All right, well, let's see what you two drew.
我們有點匆忙
We were rushed.
不是最好的 但
It's-it's not the best, but...
哇喔
Oh, wow.
什麼 你在逗我嗎 太棒了
What, are you kidding? These are amazing.
Jimmy 我完全不知道你能畫出這樣的作品
Jimmy, I had no idea you could draw like this, man.
什麼
What?
想要見識下才能嗎
Want to see talent?
看這個
Check this out.
那是你在
Is that your painting
-我們兄弟之夜畫的嗎 -沒錯
- from our guys' night out? - That's right.
棒極了 不是嗎
It's amazing, isn't it?
警方的證物袋真的給這幅畫
The, uh, police evidence bag really adds
-添加了很多現實主義色彩 -質感
- a level of realism to it. - Texture.
沒有什麼比一個死亡的海軍更現實
Nothing more real than a dead sailor.
帶上裝備
Grab your gear.
再見
See you.
嘿 讓我看看
Hey, let me see.
哦
Oh.
龍兄鼠弟畫的嗎 McGee
【注：1988年的喜劇片】
Twins paint that, McGee?
並不是 老大
Not exactly, boss.
Gibbs傷害了我 他深深傷害了我
Gibbs cut me. He cut me deep.
每個人都是批評家 走吧
Everyone's a critic. Come on.
水道志願者是個非盈利組織
Waterway Volunteers is a nonprofit
致力於清理河流和海洋垃圾
that clears trash from rivers and oceans.
拯救海龜和海豚
Saving sea turtles and dolphins
免受塑料吸管和其他東西的傷害
from, you know, plastic straws and all that.
吸管有害嗎
Straws are bad?
塑料吸管於海洋生物就是毒藥
Plastic straws are poison to sea life.
-看這個錄像 -不 不要看那個錄像
- Here, check out this video. - No, not the video.
-我沒法再看一遍了 -你又不是那個
- I can't watch that thing again. - You're not the one
氣管被合成吸管堵住的人
with a synthetic rod constricting your airway.
好了 Veronica
All right, Veronica,
Archie 讓我們回歸正題
Archie, let's stay on track.
你們倆是
What time did you guys
什麼時候到的
arrive on the scene?
上午6點
6:00 a.m.
你們看到什麼異常情況嗎
Did you guys see anything out of the ordinary?
你說屍體不算異常情況嗎
You mean other than the dead body?
實際上 等下
Actually, hold up.
你想讓我們看見什麼嗎
Did you want us to see something?
啥
What?
也許如果我們說了你想聽的
Maybe if we tell you what you want to hear,
NCIS可以代表我們給耶魯招生委員會
NCIS could write a couple of letters of commendation
寫幾封推薦信
to the Yale Admissions Board on our behalf?
好吧 耶魯
Okay. Yale?
-對 -繼續做夢吧 兄弟
- Yeah. - Keep dreaming, buddy.
有什麼發現 Palmer
What do you got, Palmer?
除了斷掉的脖子
Well, other than the broken neck,
沒有其他外在傷痕
there's no outward signs of trauma.
-Torres探員 -有死亡時間嗎
- Agent Torres. - You have time of death?
屍體的情況顯示他
Condition of the body points to him
在水裏待了一段時間
being in the water for some time.
我估計將近一個禮拜
I'd say close to a week.
我無法通過指紋確認他的身份
I wasn't able to confirm his identity using fingerprints.
孔雀魚先下手了
Yeah, the guppies got to him first.
這就是生命的輪回啊 紳士們
That is the circle of life, gentlemen.
順便說一句
I mean that in the most
我對死者還是滿懷敬意的
respectful way possible, by the way.
我們在他口袋裏找了他的士兵證
We found his military I.D. in his pocket,
根據他制服上的姓名條
and according to the name tag on his uniform,
我們的受害者是二級軍士Richard Granger
our victim is Senior Chief Richard Granger,
就任於國防後勤局
assigned to the Defense Logistics Agency.
Jethro 我給屍體做了個快速檢查
Ah, Jethro, I gave the body a quick examination.
外部並沒有
While there was no
明顯的傷痕
outward appearance of trauma...
脖子斷了
Neck is broken.
已經知道了 Duck
Already got that, Duck.
哦
Oh.
嘿 Gibbs
Hey, Gibbs.
我們有個大問題
We have a big problem.
我剛和國防後勤局通了電話
I just got off the phone with the Defense Logistics Agency,
就是二級軍士Granger工作的地方
where Senior Chief Granger worked.
知道他們為什麼沒有上報無故缺勤嗎
Any reason they didn't report him UA?
就是這個問題
That's the thing.
跟我通話的人就是二級軍士Granger
Uh, the person I spoke to was Senior Chief Granger.
他還活著
He's alive.
那他是誰
Then who is this?
你認識他嗎
Do you recognize him?
天呐
My God.
不認識 他是誰
No. Who is he?
我們也想知道
That's what we want to know.
他是怎麼拿到你的軍士證和制服的
How'd he get your military I.D. and your uniform?
我的公寓上周被非法闖入了
My apartment was broken into last week,
我的一些裝備被偷
and some of my gear was stolen.
我填了警方報告 但是沒有回音
I filed a police report, but nothing came of it.
知道為什麼有人想
Any idea why someone would want
假扮你嗎 Granger軍士
to impersonate you, Chief Granger?
毫無頭緒
Not a clue.
我是後勤倉庫的人事員
I'm a personnel clerk in a logistics depot.
不是個搶手的工作
Not exactly a sexy job,
除非你迷戀彩色編碼組織圖
unless you're into color-coded organizational charts.
稍等
Hold on.
我需要保護嗎
Do I need protection or something?
假扮我的人被殺了
A guy pretending to be me was killed.
這是我被盯上了的意思嗎
Does that mean I'm being targeted?
誰告訴你他被殺了
Who said he was killed?
沒多少人是因為自然原因死在波托馬克河的
Not many people end up in the Potomac from natural causes.
呃
Mm.
噢
Oh.
很抱歉 醫生
I am so sorry, Doctor. I...
我打算把我的東西都收走
I meant to clear all my stuff out of here
既然你已經全職回歸NCIS了
now that you're back here at NCIS full-time.
-Palmer醫生 -我知道 我知道
- Dr. Palmer. - I know, I know.
一個整齊的工作室才是高效率的工作室
An organized workspace is an efficient workspace.
是的 你說得沒錯 但我只是想評價下你的畫
Yes, it is, but I was about to commend you on this drawing.
-哦 是嗎 -是的 細節驚人
- Oh, really? - Yes, amazing detail.
我特別喜歡你
I particularly like the way you've drawn
畫上下腔靜脈的方式
the superior and inferior vena cava.
看來你拿著畫筆跟拿著手術刀
It seems you are as skillful with a pencil
一樣的靈巧熟練
as you are with a scalpel.
希望我不會把兩者混淆 那就糟了
Hopefully, I don't get the two confused. That could get messy.
沒錯
Right.
你回來真好 醫生
It's good to have you back here, Doctor.
你不在這 感覺都不一樣了
Things weren't the same around here without you.
我的圖書之旅倒是個令人愉悅的改變
Yeah, it's a welcome change from my book tour.
嗨 Ducky 你打電話了 -是的 我們的檢查結果是
Hey, Ducky. You rang? Yeah, our examination
正確的 死因是脊椎骨
was correct-- the cause of death
C3關節的骨折
was a fracture to the C3 vertebra.
但骨折不是因為墜入水中
But it wasn't from the fall into the water.
受害人在那之前就死了
The victim was dead beforehand.
所以不是自殺？
So not a suicide?
除非他能先把自己脖子
Not unless he broke his own neck
扭斷再讓自己翻滾到水裏去
and then somehow managed to roll himself into the water.
折斷自己脖子然後自己再翻滾入水
Broke his own neck and rolled himself into the water?
你知道嗎 我還沒寫過這種故事呢
You know, I don't have a story for that one.
噢 這倒是新鮮
Oh, that's never happened before.
我這會兒非常不舒服
I'm very uncomfortable right now.
哦 我也是
Oh, so am I.
請求繼續進行
Permission to proceed?
批准了
Granted.
好的 在我們的檢查過程中
All right, during our examination,
我們發現受害人的腿部有一根
we found a metal rod in the victim's leg
之前手術放入的金屬杆
from a previous surgery.
我在系統裏查了下序列號
I ran the serial number in the system,
有一個匹配的
came up with a hit.
-那麼受害人是誰 -來見過受害人
- So who's our victim? - Meet our victim
冒牌海軍 Wesley Moore 他31歲了
and Navy impersonator, Wesley Moore. He's 31.
曾是自由網絡系統工程師
He's a freelance cyber systems engineer.
未婚 無子女 無親屬
Unmarried, no kids, no next of kin,
這就解釋了為什麼
which explains why he was missing for a week
他失蹤了一周也沒人報警 -犯罪記錄呢
and no one reported it. - Criminal record?
除了一些學生貸款延遲返還 這人沒什麼問題
Other than a few late student loan payments, this guy's clean.
是的 Moore在八年前因為腿部受傷
Yeah, Moore had a brief stint in the military
離開海軍候補軍官學校之前
eight years ago before washing out
之前曾在軍中短暫服役
of Marine Officer Candidate School after a leg injury.
他遇害的那晚有什麼行動嗎
What about his movements the night he was killed?
我們根據Moore從高級軍士長Granger
We tracked Moore's steps with the I.D. he stole
那裏偷到的證件追蹤他的足跡
from Senior Chief Granger.
他用證件獲取了
He used it to gain access
進入國防部後勤署的權限
to the Defense Logistics Agency.
大門的安保鏡頭捕捉到
And security cameras at the gate
他的車在上周三
captured his vehicle entering the premises
晚上九點進入了後勤署
at 2100 hours last Wednesday.
是的 他兩個小時後離開了
Yeah, he exited two hours later.
之後  Moore去向不明
After that, Moore fell off the grid.
對車的通緝令已經發出去了
BOLO's already out on the car.
他為什麼要溜進國防部後勤署呢
Why'd he sneak into the DLA?
為了黑進國防部的保密通信
To hack into the DoD's classified message traffic.
我在查他獲取了哪些信息
I'm working on what he accessed,
但是海外軍隊部署相關的
but sensitive data on troops' movements overseas
敏感信息可能已經泄露了
might have been compromised.
而且我們手上有一個嚴重的安全漏洞
And we got a serious security breach on our hands.
是 我是Gibbs
Yeah, it's Gibbs.
Hi Gibbs 你有時間嗎
Hi, Gibbs. Do you have a minute?
好的 馬上下去
Yeah, be right down.
找出Moore在追蹤什麼
Find out what Moore was after.
水流情況
Water currents?
是的 我還以為一個造船的人
Yeah, you'd think a person who builds boats
會覺得潮汐變化十分美妙
would find tide shifts more fascinating.
一條線索更能吸引我
A lead would be fascinating.
這就是線索
This is the lead.
怎麼 你以為我讓你下來
What, did you think I invited you down here
就是為了有趣的無聲交流嗎
for some riveting nonverbal conversation?
好吧 呃 繼續
Okay, uh, moving on.
我在分析過去六天的海岸
So, I have been analyzing the coastal tide patterns
潮汐模式
for the past six days,
從Moore屍體沖上岸的地方倒推
working backwards from where Wesley Moore's body washed up
看他的屍體從哪裏入水的
to determine where his body first entered the water.
-縮小搜查範圍 -嘿
- Narrowed down the search grid. - Hey!
現在我們終於合拍了
Now we're on the same wavelength.
好吧
Okay.
但你不喜歡雙關 好的 很高興知道這點
And not a fan of puns. Okay, um, good to know.
好吧 如果我的計算是正確的
Okay, if my calculations are correct,
Moore的屍體是在
Moore's body was dumped
距北部舊城附近海岸線兩英裏的範圍內
somewhere within a two-mile stretch of shoreline near...
被拋下水的
North Old Town.
呃 Gibbs 我有一些發現了
Uh, Gibbs, I've got something.
Wesley Moore的郵件和通話記錄表明
Wesley Moore's e-mail and phone records indicate
他接到了一位駐紮在阿富汗喀布爾的
he received several messages from Captain Alicia Voit,
Alicia Voit上尉的一些信息
a Marine stationed in Kabul, Afghanistan.
在他們兩周前的
And in their last correspondence,
最後一次通信中 Voit給Moore發了一封
two weeks ago, Voit e-mailed Moore
包含12名死亡軍人姓名的電子郵件
the names of 12 dead Marines.
別告訴我又是一個刺殺清單
Please tell me this is not another hit list.
不是
No.
不是那樣 那些軍人在Voit
Not so much. All of those Marines died
發郵件之前就死亡了
prior to Voit's message being sent.
她為什麼把死亡軍人的
Why would she message a list
名單發給Moore呢
of deceased Marines' names to Moore?
聯系喀布爾的基地
Contact the base in Kabul.
-在MTAC裏接通Voit -呃 Gibbs
- Get Voit on MTAC. - Uh, Gibbs,
這沒法實現
that's impossible.
Alicia Voit上尉在六天前的一次行動裏遇害了
Captain Alicia Voit was killed in action six days ago,
和我們的受害者Wesley Moore
same day as our victim,
同一天死亡
Wesley Moore.
Alicia Voit上尉 30歲
Captain Alicia Voit, 30,
一位被高度評價的軍人
a highly decorated Marine
這是她第三次在阿富汗服役
who was serving her third tour in Afghanistan.
六天前在喀布爾城外
She was killed six days ago
她的護送隊被塔利班叛軍伏擊後
after her convoy was ambushed by Taliban insurgents
她也遇害身亡
just outside of Kabul.
這次襲擊是
The attack was led
Aazar Atwa領導的
by Aazar Atwa,
一個該為去年多名美軍的
an extremist responsible for multiple
傷亡負責的極端分子
U.S. casualties over the past year.
Voit上尉的屍體被送到了多佛空軍基地
Captain Voit's body was sent to Dover Air Force Base.
她的遺體計劃於明天運回
Her remains are set to be released tomorrow.
她和Wesley Moore有什麼關系
What's her connection to Wesley Moore?
他們是八年前在海軍候選軍官
They met at Marine Officer Candidate School
學校認識的
eight years ago.
Moore被項目刷下來了 但他們一直很親近
Moore washed out of the program, but the two remained close.
他們肯定不止是同學關系
They were definitely more than that.
我是說 根據他們的郵件往來和發的社交網站來看
I mean, by their e-mails and social media posts,
沒錯 他們肯定關系不一般
yeah, they were definitely involved.
呣 我讀過那些郵件
Um, I read those letters.
他們之間沒什麼浪漫關系
There was nothing romantic in them.
Bishop
Bishop.
單身男 單身女 你自己算
Single guy, single girl. Do the math.
最新消息 Torres
News flash, Torres.
呃 男人和女人之間是可以有純潔的關系的
Uh, men and women can have platonic relationships.
為什麼
Why?
McGee Moore具體從國防部後勤署黑到了哪些信息
McGee, what about the Intel Moore hacked from the DLA?
他拿到了與Voit上尉在最後一封郵件
He accessed the non-redacted after-action reports
裏發給他的在行動中遇害的12名軍人
on the 12 K.I.A. Marines
相關的未加密的事後報告
Captain Voit listed in her last e-mail to him.
這些軍人都死於Aazar Atwa之前的襲擊中
All were victims of Aazar Atwa's previous attacks.
Torres 重點關注Kasie劃出的搜查區域
Torres, focus on Kasie's search grid.
找到Moore是在哪裏被拋屍的
Find out where Moore's body was dumped.
McGee  Bishop拿上你們的應急包
McGee, Bishop, get your go-bags.
-應急包 -噢 去哪裏
- Go-bags? - Oh, where are we going?
阿富汗
Afghanistan.
敬 禮
Present arms!
立 正
Order arms!
向左向右 轉
Right or left, face!
向前進
Forward march!
你應該就是Gibbs探員了
You must be Agent Gibbs.
總部通知我們等你來 我是Park上校
HQ said to expect you. Colonel Park.
你是被指派給Voit上尉的護衛嗎
You're the Marine escort assigned to Captain Voit?
是的 我的任務是最後一次送她回家
Affirmative. I am tasked with her final transit home.
上尉的遺體一小時內應該就會被放行
The captain's remains should be released within the hour.
出什麼問題了嗎
Something wrong?
上校不常被分派這類任務吧
Colonels aren't usually assigned these details.
軍人以服從命令為天職
A Marine goes where he's needed,
Gibbs探員
Agent Gibbs.
你的目的地是哪裏
What's your destination?
新澤西州的Strathmere  Voit上尉的家鄉
Strathmere, New Jersey. Captain Voit's hometown.
我們會在10點鍾出發
Our transport will be departing at 1000 hours.
上校 恐怕你們的出發要推遲了
Colonel, I'm afraid there's going to be a delay.
-為什麼 -Voit上尉現在是我們正在調查的
- Excuse me? - Captain Voit
一起謀殺案調的一部分了
is now part of an active murder investigation.
謀殺調查
Murder investigation?
這件事沒人告訴過我
I wasn't informed of that.
她的遺體需要送到
Her remains are to be brought
NCIS 直到我們找到更多的答案
to NCIS until we have more answers.
我能理解
I understand your...
你的境遇 Gibbs探員
your situation, Agent Gibbs,
但我不能允許此事發生
but I cannot allow that.
這不是請求 上校
It's not a request, Colonel.
我的任務是把上尉送回家
It's my duty to get the captain home
讓她在兩天之內得到安息
to be laid to rest in two days.
而我也會盡我所能確保此事按期執行
And I'll do everything I can to ensure that happens.
無意冒犯 但是我覺得這並不夠
With all due respect, that's not good enough for me.
上校 Voit上尉的死可能與
Colonel, there's a possibility that Captain Voit's death
另一起謀殺案有關
is connected to another murder case.
我們需要給兩名受害者
We owe it to both victims
找出真相
to find out the truth.
這一點上我們的追求是一致的
That is something we do agree on.
好吧
All right.
但是我要跟你一起
But I'm going with you.
別指望我能離開上尉半步
Don't expect me to leave the captain's side.
明白
Understood.
這是什麼泥啊
What kind of mud is this?
感覺就像流沙
It feels like quicksand.
你確定搜索範圍是在這裏嗎
Are you sure this is the right search grid?
非常確定 Moore的屍體一定是在 大概 這附近
Oh, yeah, positive. Moore's body had to have entered the water,
掉進了水裏
like, around here.
哦 我天 哦 我的天呐
Oh, my... oh, my... oh, my God! Oh, my God!
哦 天呐 你看到那些蒼蠅有多大了嗎
Oh, my God, did you see the size of that fly?
看起來就像史前生物
It was, like, prehistoric.
呃 就把這當成你成為外勤探員的速成課程
Uh, consider this your crash course on field agent work.
是啊 被油汙覆蓋 還要
Yeah, okay, well, getting covered in grime and, like,
被蒼蠅吃掉 並不是很符合你說的
eaten by flies isn't exactly the high-octane experience
-及其新穎的體驗啊 -時間還長著呢 姐們兒
- you promised. - The day's young, sister.
好吧 但是如果我看見哪怕一條蛇 我就...
Fine, but if I see one snake, I am...
我就離開這裏
I'm out of here.
等等 蛇嗎 你是在 等一下 你什麼意思 有蛇嗎
Wait, snake? What are you... Wait, what do you mean, snake?
你說蛇是什麼意思
What are you talking about, snakes?
哦 沒錯 它們在沼澤系統裏繁衍生息
Oh, yeah. They thrive in swampy ecosystems.
好了 好吧
All right, okay.
呃 繼續堅持
Well, uh... stay on it.
搞完這裏 我要 我馬上回來
Get 'er done. I'm gonna... I'll be right back.
在恐怖電影裏 一般說這話的人
Yeah, that's usually what someone says
馬上就會死掉
right before they're killed in a horror movie,
但是 我確定這完全不一樣
but yeah, I'm sure this is totally different.
我愛我的工作 我愛我的工作 我愛我的工作
I love my job, I love my job, I love my job,
我愛我的工作 哦
I love my job. Oof!
嗨 夥計
Hey, man.
能跟你說句話嗎
Can I have a word?
嗨 終於來了啊
Hey, it's about time.
整早就我一個人在這裏
Been out here on my own all morning.
怎麼 還需要我發一張請柬嗎
What, are you waiting for an invitation?
開始幹活啊
Start pulling your weight.
先把問題放一放 夥計 我是NCIS
Okay, take it down a notch, buddy. NCIS.
抱歉 我 呃
Sorry about that. I, uh...
我以為你是我們的志願者呢
I thought you were one of our volunteers.
他遲到一個半小時了
He's over an hour and a half late.
你是 呃 Waterway志願者協會的成員嗎
Are you with, uh, Waterway Volunteers?
呃 沒錯
Uh, yeah. That's right.
我花了一早晨的時間
I spent my morning covering
清理那條半英裏的路
a half-mile stretch that way.
怎麼回事 NCIS在這裏幹什麼
Why? What's NCIS doing out here?
Nick 我有發現了
Nick! Got something!
你說過Wesley Moore開著一輛什麼車來著
What kind of car did you say Wesley Moore had?
銀色福特福克斯
It's a silver Ford Focus.
不錯啊 Kasie
Not bad, Kasie.
謝謝
Thanks.
為什麼一個像Voit上尉這樣的授勳陸戰隊員
Why would a decorated Marine like Captain Voit get mixed up
會跟Wesley Moore這樣的人混在一起呢
with somebody like Wesley Moore?
他們並沒那麼不同 Leon
Well, they're not that different, Leon.
都在十幾歲成為孤兒 生長在社會福利機構裏的孩子
Both were orphaned as teenagers, were children of public servants
而且都有這種純潔的為國效力的願望
and shared this pure desire to serve their country.
我們說的是同一個Moore嗎
Are we talking about the same Moore?
那個假扮成海軍水手
The one who impersonated a Navy sailor,
闖入設防的軍事設施
who broke onto a secure military facility
黑進了機密的國防部服務器
and hacked into a confidential DoD server,
把數千美軍士兵置於危險境地的那個人嗎
putting thousands of U.S. troops at risk?
嗨 我沒說他是完美的人
Hey, I didn't say he was perfect.
這麼說就非常輕描淡寫了
Well, there's an understatement.
但我不相信 Moore
But I don't believe that Moore
侵入那些文件是出於邪惡的原因
accessed those files for nefarious reasons.
他確實幫了Voit
He-he did it to help Voit.
怎麼幫的
Help how?
Voit是在尋找答案
Voit was looking for answers.
沒錯 關於12個死掉的陸戰隊員的
Right. On the 12 dead Marines.
她知道Moore
She knew that Moore
能夠黑進國防部系統
could hack into DoD's system
還不用顧忌那些繁文縟節
and cut through the governmental red tape.
沒錯 只是這非常不合法
Yeah, in a highly illegal way.
這意味著事情非常緊迫
Which suggests a sense of urgency.
Voit上尉找Moore求助
Now, Captain Voit reached out to Moore
而不是去找她的指揮系統 為什麼呢
instead of going through her chain of command. Why?
因為Voit不知道能夠相信誰
'Cause Voit didn't know who to trust.
沒錯
Exactly.
你認為他們的死是有關聯的嗎
You think their deaths are connected?
百分百確信
100%.
他們都死在了同一天
They both died the same day--
一個死在華盛頓 一個死在阿富汗
one in D.C., one in Afghanistan.
協同攻擊 對吧
Coordinated attacks, yeah?
這一切的關鍵一定跟阿富汗那邊有關
And the key to why has to do with Afghanistan.
一般在這個時候你就會告訴我
And this is usually the time you tell me
你已經派人前往阿富汗了
that you've already sent a team en route.
今早就派遣McGee和Bishop去了
Sent McGee and Bishop this morning.
他們應該隨時會到達Russell營地
They should be at Camp Russell any minute.
別問我 我也不知道他是怎麼做到的
Don't ask me. I-I don't know how he does it, either.
已經向將軍彙報過情況了
The CG's been briefed on the situation.
他讓全力配合
He said to assist in any way possible.
-我們能跟他談談嗎 -他剛剛在跟
- When can we speak with him? - Well, he's finishing up
今天新到的陸戰特遣小隊談話
with a new Marine detachment that arrived today.
我以為美軍應該
Thought, uh, U.S. forces were supposed to be
-開始從阿富汗撤軍了 -確實是這麼計劃的
- withdrawing from Afghanistan. - That was the plan.
但是塔利班的襲擊一直在增加
But with the Taliban's attacks increasing
而且他們對喀布爾的控制一直在鞏固
and their grip on Kabul strengthening,
撤軍行動已經被推遲了
the withdrawal's been put on hold.
所依你跟Aazar Atwa很熟是嗎
So you're familiar with Aazar Atwa?
是的 女士 大概沒有陸戰隊員
Yes, ma'am. You'd be hard-pressed to find
跟他不熟
a Marine here who isn't.
他害死了很多我們的人
We've lost a lot of good people because of him.
Voit上尉只是最近的傷亡
Captain Voit was just the most recent casualty.
你可以說Atwa是這裏的頭號公敵
You could say Atwa is public enemy number one around here.
Bishop和McGee探員
Agents Bishop and McGee.
我是Braxton將軍 Russell營地的指揮官
Russell的I'm General Braxton, CG of Camp Russell.
-非常感謝您的協助 將軍 -當然
- Appreciate the assistance, General. - Of course.
Voit上尉是我們自己人
Captain Voit was one of our own.
我們希望能給她伸張正義
We want her to have justice.
看來你們來得正是時候 剛好可以目睹我們伸張正義
And it looks like you both have arrived just in time to see it.
這怎麼說
How's that?
我從我們的巡邏隊得到消息
I received word from our patrol
他們在東北扇區發現了一個疑似塔利班安全屋
in the northeast sector who were conducting a raid
並進行了突襲
of a suspected Taliban safe house.
-他們找到武器藏匿地點了嗎 -比這更好
- Did they find the weapons cache? - Better.
他們找到了Aazar Atwa
They found Aazar Atwa.
Atwa現在在哪呢
Wh-Where's Atwa now?
正在返回我們基地的路上 有重兵把守
En route back to our base, under heavy guard.
你們對Voit上尉的死有疑問嗎
You have questions about Captain Voit's death?
你們很快就有機會面對面地詢問
You'll soon get the chance to question her killer
殺害她的凶手了
face-to-face.
你確定不需要我做什麼嗎 上校
Are you sure there's nothing I can get for you, Colonel?
不 謝謝你 我很好
No. Thank you. I'm fine.
你是否介意我問一下 呃 包裏是什麼
Do you mind me asking what's, uh... what's in the bag?
Voit上尉的私人物品
Contains Captain Voit's personal effects.
啊 是啊 我忍不住注意到
Ah. Yeah, I couldn't help but notice that...
你一分一秒都不讓它離開你的視線
you won't let it out of your sight, even for a second.
根據國防部規定
Per DoD regulations,
逝去軍人的私人物品
a fallen service member's personal effects
應當全程由護送者守護
shall remain in the escort's possession at all times
直到送達親人手中
until directly delivered to the next of kin.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
要知道 對陸戰隊員而言 我想不出
You know, I can't imagine a more difficult detail for a Marine
會有比護送逝去的兄弟姐妹回家 更難受的任務了
to be assigned than escorting a fallen brother or sister home.
我想你們的工作跟這相比也沒什麼不同 醫生
I suspect your job is not much different, Doctor.
是啊 會有...有時會有一些內心的掙紮
Yeah. It's a, uh... it's a struggle at times.
但是當我知道我們在幫忙提供一些結論
But I take comfort in knowing that we're helping
這會讓我內心舒服一些
to provide with some closure.
我內心舒適與否無關緊要
My comfort is inconsequential.
那些為國家
Those that make the ultimate sacrifice
犧牲一切的人
for this country
理應載著榮譽返回家中
deserve to be brought home with honor.
Duck 有什麼發現
Duck, what do we know?
Voit上尉的檢查
An examination of Captain Voit
沒有什麼結果
could not be performed since
因為要舉行葬禮 她的屍體被處理過了
she has already been processed for burial.
但是Kabul和Dover的記錄
But the records from Kabul and Dover
十分詳細
are very thorough.
上尉先被兩顆子彈擊中胸部
The captain was first struck with two bullets to the chest.
盡管她嚴重受傷
Uh, despite her grave condition,
但在第三次致命的頭部打擊前
she managed to take out four insurgents
她成功地擊敗四名恐怖分子
before the third and fatal blow to the head.
她從沒放棄
She never gave up.
這就是陸戰隊員
That's a Marine.
好了 夠了
Okay. We are done here.
-上校 -我遵守了你的要求
- Colonel? - I complied with your request,
Gibbs探員 我同意你將Voit上尉帶到這裏來
Agent Gibbs. I allowed you to bring Captain Voit here,
來反駁我的判斷
against my better judgment.
你的法醫剛才說
As your doctors have just pointed out,
她對你們來說已經沒有用了
she is of no further use to you.
把她的遺物給我 讓我
Release her remains, and allow me
完成我的任務
to finish my mission.
證物還在處理中
Evidence is still being processed.
調查還沒結束
Our investigation isn't over.
但我的合作結束了
But my cooperation is.
你們兩位單獨談談吧
W-We'll give you two a moment.
-這是什麼 -備忘錄
- What's this? - A memo,
來自於國防部長
from the Secretary of Defense,
以確保你的配合
ensuring your full cooperation.
解釋下為什麼上尉在阿富汗的時候
Explain to me how the captain can be involved
會卷入一場美國的謀殺案
in a murder in the States when she was in Afghanistan.
這說不通
This makes no sense.
我在盡我的職責
I'm doing my job!
我以為你是名陸戰隊員 Gibbs
I thought you were a Marine, Gibbs.
你若是 就把她送回去
If you were, you'd have her back.
她的葬禮將在36小時後舉行
Her burial is in 36 hours.
我會把她送到那裏的
I will get her there.
嘿 Kasie
Hey, Kasie.
怎麼樣
How you doing?
情緒範圍一到十嗎
On a scale of one to ten?
是負數
We're in the negatives.
-哇 -你說說
- Whoa. - Yeah, tell me about it.
我想成為名外勤特工 結果卻被咬了
I tried being a field agent, and it bit me.
你看看
Look at me.
就像個連接點圖
It's like a connect-the-dots sheet.
我沒在笑
I'm not really laughing.
好吧 既然工作是少有的幾件能讓我
Okay, well, since work is one of the only things
忘記癢的事
distracting me from the urge to itch,
我要開始了
I'm just gonna jump right in.
我在Wesley Moore的車上沒有發現任何有用的指紋
I didn't find any usable prints in Wesley Moore's car,
但我在損壞的後車身上有發現
but I hit the jackpot with the rear body damage.
看下這個
Check this out.
這是Moore在他被殺的那晚
This is a surveillance image
離開國防後勤局的
of Moore leaving the DLA
監控錄像 注意到了什麼嗎
on the night that he was killed. You notice anything?
-尾燈和擋板完好無損 -對
- Taillight and fender are intact. - Yeah.
說明這輛車是在他死前那晚的
Meaning this vehicle was damaged later that night,
晚些時候損壞的
before he was killed.
所以 如果他被盯上了 凶手一定
So, if he was being tailed, the killer must have, uh,
撞上擋板讓Moore下車
caused a fender bender to get Moore out of the car.
所以我得到了第二份油漆的信息
So I pulled a second paint profile
是剛說的凶手的車 哇
of the killer's car in question. Whoo!
想試著五倍速說完
Try saying that five times fast.
是有金屬底漆的紅漆
And it is a lacquer-based red with a metallic base coat.
符合這樣的車數不過來
Okay, hundreds of cars match that.
實際上 因為它是生產中最常用的
Actually, since it's one of the most used
油漆類型之一
paint types in production,
數量就更加多了
the number's more in the thousands.
你看我們該怎麼縮小嫌犯範圍
How do you suggest we narrow down our suspects?
靠堅持不懈的努力 聰明才智
Well, with, uh, persistence, diligence,
結合電腦技術
and our combined computer skills.
結合嗎 我嗎 Bishop 還是McGee
Combined? What am I, Bishop or McGee?
不可能 我就是個
No, I'm more of, like,
運動份子
a physical specimen, man, you know?
打架 恐嚇別人
You know, punching, intimidating,
-才是符合我做的事 -好吧
- that's more my thing. - Mm, okay.
我替你穿過了那片沼澤 Nicholas
I trekked through a swamp for you, Nicholas.
所以 你要是不替我擔保 就會在
So, if you bail on me now, you're just gonna find
辦公桌抽屜裏發現會動的銅頭蛇
a slithering copperhead snake in your desk drawer.
或者在你的床上
Ooh, or in your bed.
或者更糟
Or worse.
只有我
Is it just me,
-感覺到 -太過容易了嗎
- or does this feel... - Too easy?
不僅是你有這種感覺
No, it's not just you.
作為被捕的恐怖分子他看上去很自在
He looks pretty carefree for a captured terrorist.
你來翻譯嗎
You gonna translate?
不 我不需要
No. I don't need to,
因為他能聽得懂
'cause he can understand us just fine.
是嗎
Isn't that right?
是的 我能聽懂
Yes, I can.
不好意思 什麼東西逗樂你了嗎
Sorry, does something amuse you?
所有的這些
This. All of it.
給你看看我不覺得有趣的東西
Well, let me show you what I don't find funny.
Alicia Voit
Alicia Voit,
Max Wiezman
Max Wiezman,
Anna Gutierrez
Anna Gutierrez,
Tyson Eccles和Nolan Takahamo
Tyson Eccles, Nolan Takahamo.
還要繼續嗎
Should I continue?
-這些名字對我來說沒什麼意義 -它們應該有
- Those names mean nothing to me. - Well, they should.
這些是你殺死的陸戰隊員的名字
They're the names of some of the Marines you killed.
再說一遍
Again...
它們對我來說沒有什麼意義
...they mean nothing to me.
所以你不否認你殺了他們
So you don't deny it?
為什麼要否認值得我驕傲的事呢
Why deny what I'm proud of?
要是你這麼驕傲 跟我們說一下她
Well, if you're so proud, tell us about her.
她是上周你襲擊的運輸隊成員之一
She was part of the convoy you hit last week.
我記得
I remember.
那天天氣晴朗
The sky was so clear that day.
我們從很遠就能看到他們的車子
We could see their vehicle from miles away,
她真是不幸
unfortunately for her.
那也不容易吧
Wasn't that easy.
Voit上尉殺了你的四個手下
Captain Voit killed four of your men
在你殺死她前
before you could finish her off.
我猜你低估了她
Guess you underestimated her.
我們要繼續這場遊戲嗎
Are we going to continue this game,
還是想知道我襲擊的真相
or do you want to know the truth about my attacks?
告訴我們
Tell us.
你們要給我想要的
Only if I get something in return.
自由
My freedom.
真新奇
How original.
你是個恐怖分子 殺了13名陸戰隊員
You're a terrorist who killed 13 U.S. Marines.
希望你能好好享受鐐銬
Hope you enjoy those shackles,
因為你要在監獄裏
'cause you're gonna be living in a cell
度過餘生了 我們走
for the rest of your life. Let's go.
我從一個美國人那裏
I had help,
得到了幫助
from an American.
引起你們的注意了嗎
Now do I have your attention?
你和美國人一起合作嗎
You were working with an American?
證明下
Prove it.
用我的自由來換
My freedom for a traitor
背叛國家的叛徒
who's been betraying your country.
一場公平的交易
Fair trade,
不覺得嗎
don't you think?
Atwa瘋了
Atwa's out of his damn mind.
美國政府不會和恐怖分子做交易
The U.S. government will not d a deal with a known terrorist.
我明白 主任 但是Atwa說
I understand, Director, but Atwa claims
他一直在和一個內部的美國人合作
he's been working with an American on the inside.
Atwa很聰明
Atwa's smart.
他會說出我們想要聽到的東西
He'll say whatever we want to hear
只要能確保他被釋放
if it means securing his release.
我們不能保證他給我們的是真的
We have no guarantee what he gives us is the truth.
通常來說 Sloane 我會同意你說的
Yes, and normally, Sloane, I would agree with you,
但這次我不同意 我覺得他不像在說謊
but not this time. I-I really don't think he's bluffing.
Bishop 發現了些什麼
Bishop, what do you know?
我以前也面對過像Atwa這樣的恐怖分子
Look, I-I've dealt with insurgents like Atwa before.
他不焦慮 緊張 反複無常
He-he's not agitated, nervous or volatile.
實際上 他很自信
He is, in fact, assured,
就像是知道自己的優勢
like someone who knows that they have the advantage.
那12個死去了的陸戰隊員呢
12 dead Marines.
他們怎麼了
What about them?
塔利班襲擊了運輸隊
Transports were hit by the Taliban.
在最後時刻運輸路線改變了
Convoy routes are changed at the last minute.
是的
Yeah.
一定有人把他們的行動
Someone had to be directly relaying
直接告訴了Atwa
their movements to Atwa.
即使是真的 也無法抹去
Well, even if that's true, it doesn't erase the fact
Atwa殺死那些隊員的事實
that Atwa's caused the deaths of multiple troops.
Leon 他想要對話
He wants to talk, Leon.
那就讓他說 但不會有交易的
Well, then get him to talk, but he's not getting a deal.
明白了嗎
Is that clear?
明白了 主任
Uh, yes, yes, Director.
Gibbs
Gibbs?
他的朋友不需要知道
His friends don't need to know that.
上校 太晚了
Colonel, it's late.
在宿舍給你准備了個房間
Got a room waiting for you at the BOQ.
這沒必要 我很好
That won't be necessary. I'm doing fine.
國防部護送人員可以
DoD escorts are permitted
將遺體留在
to leave service members' remains
安全的地方
at a secure location.
我知道規章
I know what the regulations say.
我只是覺得只留下上尉一個人在這裏不好
I just don't feel right leaving the captain alone.
知道你會這麼說
Yeah, figured you were gonna say something like that.
你在做什麼
What are you doing?
給你搭張床
I'm getting you a cot.
-我說了 我很好 -我知道 你很好
- I told you, I'm fine. - Yeah, yeah, I know, you're fine.
我明白
I got it, okay.
你得睡覺
Got to sleep somewhere.
要麼這裏 要麼離開
Hey, take it or leave it.
你決定
Your call.
我為之前說過的話
I owe you an apology
道歉 Gibbs
for what I said earlier, Gibbs.
我不該質疑你的忠誠
It was wrong to question your service.
我去過那裏 上校
I've been there, Colonel.
分配到護送任務
It is not easy
很不容易
getting assigned an escort detail.
是啊
No.
不容易
No, it's not.
要是你是自願的就更加艱難了
It's even harder if you volunteered for it.
那麼明顯嗎
Was it that obvious?
你怎麼認識Voit上尉的
How'd you know Captain Voit?
是我招募了她
I was the one who recruited her.
十年前我遇到了Voit
Met Voit ten years ago.
在前一個冬天她失去了雙親
She had just lost both of her parents the winter before.
她正在上大學
She was putting herself through college.
工作認真 頭腦聰明
She was a real hard worker, and good head on her shoulders.
是塊做陸戰隊的料
Marine material.
我可以在
I can always tell within a...
在見到別人的一分鍾內
within a minute of meeting somebody
分辨出有沒有做陸戰隊員的潛質
whether they have what it takes.
Voit具有這種潛質
Voit did.
我讓她
I was the one
加入軍隊
who swore her in,
所以也應該帶她回家
so I should be the one to bring her home,
就像我為其他人死去的隊員
just like I did for all the other
做的一樣
fallen Marines that I've recruited.
有多少
How many?
一個就已經夠多的了
One is too many.
上校 他們的死不是你的責任
You're not responsible for their deaths, Colonel.
你也失去過戰友 對嗎
You've lost people, right?
在陸戰隊的時候
As a Marine,
當探員的時候
as an agent?
你覺得你沒有責任嗎
Did you not feel responsible?
他們只是 只是孩子
They were just... just kids who...
在我的引導下參了軍
joined the military under my guidance.
我每天都想著
I'll carry their deaths with me
他們的死亡
every day.
我欠他們太多了
I owe them that much.
-我們要去哪裏 -把你轉移
- Where are we going? - Transferring you.
到關塔那摩 在古巴
To Guantanamo Bay, Cuba.
希望你會喜歡那裏的潮濕和孤獨
Hope you like humidity and solitary.
這是在恐嚇我嗎
Is that supposed to frighten me?
不是 但把你和Gibbs關在一起就是了
No, but putting you in a cell with Gibbs may.
最後的機會 Atwa
Last chance, Atwa.
告訴我們和你合作的美國人是誰
Tell us the American you're working with.
-除非把我放了 -你得好好想想
- Not until I'm released. - May want to rethink that.
我想你的同伴看到你和我們合作
I can't imagine your fellow insurgents would look favorably
可不會開心
on you working with us.
他們才不關心一個美國人的命運
The fate of an American isn't their concern.
他們知道我不會背叛他們
They know I would never betray them.
除非我們在城裏散播消息
Well, unless we spread word around town
說你為了自由背叛了他們
that you gave them up for your freedom.
我們可以令人信服
We can be very convincing.
他們會認為你是個叛徒和麻煩
They'll see you as a traitor and a liability.
沒有完美的保護
You won't last one minute outside those gates,
你走出監獄活不過一分鍾
not without our protection.
所以 你要是想活著
So, if you enjoy breathing,
我建議你
I suggest you start talking
告訴我們那個美國聯絡人是誰
and tell us who your American contact is.
很好
Very well.
12個月前 我從線人那裏收到情報
12 months ago, I began receiving intelligence from a source.
發生了什麼 McGee
What the hell happened, McGee?
狙擊手從山上開的槍
Sniper fire from the mountains.
沒有人看到凶手
No one had eyes on the shooter.
Atwa告訴了你什麼嗎
Did Atwa give you anything?
他剛要說 就被中槍了
He was about to when the gunfire started.
有人想要他閉嘴
Well, someone wanted to shut him up.
這說明我們中有內奸
Which means we got a mole on our hands
他受過狙擊訓練
with advanced sniper training.
太好了
That's perfect.
轉移Atwa的消息沒有流出過Russell營地
The details of Atwa's transfer never left Camp Russell.
那一定是營內的人
So it had to be someone in-house.
Bishop正在查看所有人員的個人檔案
Bishop's going through all the personnel files now.
聽著 McGee 給我找到他
Listen to me, McGee, you find him!
我沒法再盯著屏幕了
I'm not sure I can stare at this screen much longer.
這光讓我不停地眯眼
This glare is making me squint,
這張臉不會長皺紋
and this face doesn't do wrinkles.
加油 大家
Come on, team.
即便我們通宵
Sure, we pulled an all-nighter
查交通監控 也沒找到
combing traffic-cam footage, and we're no closer
嫌疑人 但我們在一起奮斗 不是嗎
to finding our suspect, but we're in this together, right?
-朋友互相幫忙 -Jimmy
- Friends helping friends. - Jimmy,
閉嘴
stop talking.
嘿 Jimmy
Hey, Jimmy.
你什麼時候來的
When'd you get here?
哦 天啊
Oh, boy.
早上好
The top o' the morning to you.
我給你們帶了急需的食物
I bring much-needed sustenance.
兩杯黑咖啡
Two black coffees.
給
There we are. And, uh,
還有一杯大杯雙份冰摩卡
one large double mocha
加了混合奶油
frozen blend with whipping cream
巧克力片和焦糖
and chocolate chips, and a drizzle of caramel.
太棒了
Yes. Mm.
這個直擊我心
Now, that hits the spot.
你這麼吃還長這樣嗎
You can eat that and still look like that?
天啊 生活真是不公平
Man, life's not fair.
Jimmy 你讓我反感了
Jimmy, uh, you disgust me.
嘿 有發現
Hey... got something.
紅色卡車符合我們的描述
Red truck matching our description.
保險杠也損壞了
Ooh, complete with front bumper damage.
這是在哪裏拍到的
Where was this picture taken?
攝像頭 在Moore被殺的那晚
Traffic cam, ten miles from where
距離發現他車的地方
Moore's car was found
十英裏處
on the night he was killed.
這輛卡車登記在誰的名下
Who's the truck registered to?
Xavier Blackburn
Xavier Blackburn.
來自Falls Church的市民
Civilian from Falls Church.
我在沼澤地裏遇到過這家夥
Hey, I ran into this guy at the marsh.
他說他是和水路志願者一起的
He said he was with Waterway Volunteers.
Xavier Blackburn不在他們的成員名單上
Uh, there's no Xavier Blackburn listed on their crew roster.
那麼他在沼澤地裏做什麼
Then what was he doing at the marsh?
和所有犯了罪的人做同樣的事
Doing what all guilty people do.
掩蓋行跡
Covering his tracks.
你看我說得對不對
So, let me see if I got this right.
用自己的時間做志願服務 卻成為了謀殺嫌犯嗎
Volunteering my time makes me a murder suspect?
真不愧是好人難做啊
Talk about "no good deed."
但是Waterway志願服務隊裏
Okay, so no one at Waterway Volunteers
沒人聽說過你
has ever heard of you.
我是新人 他們一定搞丟了我的文件
I'm new. They must have lost my paperwork.
我們沒丟
We didn't.
Xavier Blackburn 33歲
"Xavier Blackburn, 33."
給阿靈頓一個私人軍事公司
Spent six years as a contractor
當了六年的承包商
for a private military firm in Arlington.
直到你因為行為問題
Until you were fired
被開除
because of behavioral issues.
愈演愈烈的暴力行為
"Increasingly violent outbursts
和公然無視協議
and blatant disregard for protocol."
我偶爾會跟一些目光短淺的上級
I had an occasional disagreement
有一些意見分歧
with a few short-sighted superiors.
我想你能理解
I'm sure you can relate.
不錯的貨車
Nice truck.
至少曾經不錯 我們追查它
At least it was. We... we tracked it down
查到你家附近一個汽車修理廠
to a body shop near your house.
你猜怎樣
And guess what.
你保險杠上的漆跟Wesley Moore的車相符
The paint on your bumper was a match to Wesley Moore's car.
Moore盜竊美國情報
Moore stole U.S. intelligence.
你們知道這個嗎
Did you know that?
他對國家安全是個威脅
He was a risk to national security
需要被阻止
and needed to be stopped.
Moore是在調查一起
Moore was investigating an American
美國人協助塔利班的事件
who was aiding the Taliban.
他不是叛徒 人才
He wasn't the traitor, genius.
不 你們錯了 他告訴我Moore很危險
No, you're wrong. He told me Moore was dangerous.
他
He?
他說如果我消除這個威脅
He said that if I neutralized the threat,
他就會重新雇傭我 我就能拿回我的工作了
he would reinstate me, and I would get my job back.
誰給你下的指示
Who gave you the order?
巡邏隊在5點出發
The patrol will leave at 0500 hours.
Jennings 你開頭車
Jennings, you're driving lead.
Dunne和Falconio 你們在側翼
Dunne and Falconio, you're on the flank.
-Kinneman -在
- Kinneman. - Yeah.
眼睛盯緊叛軍活動
Keep your eyes peeled for insurgent activity.
Atwa之死的謠言毫無疑問
Rumors of Atwa's death are no doubt
正在全城流傳
circulating throughout the city,
所以肯定會有報複行為
so retribution is expected.
這你倒是說對了
You're right about that.
我很抱歉 探員們 但是這是一次安全簡報
I'm sorry, Agents, but this is a secure briefing.
太晚了 將軍
It's too late for that, General.
你的巡邏路線已經被破壞了
Your patrol route's already been compromised,
而且不是我們破壞的
and not by us.
你在說什麼
What are you talking about?
繼續啊 告訴他們
Go ahead, tell 'em.
我不知道你們什麼意思
I don't know what you mean.
好吧 我給你個提示
All right, I'll give you a hint.
一個詞 第一個字是 叛
One word, begins with the letter "T."
第二個字是 國
Rhymes with "reason."
最好有人馬上解釋一下這一切
Well, someone better start making sense real soon.
這位Kinneman把你們的運輸路線
Kinneman here was leaking your transport routes
泄露給了Aazar Atwa
to Aazar Atwa.
他們在撒謊
That's a lie.
真的嗎 好吧
Really? All right.
這人看起來眼熟嗎
Does this guy look familiar?
你的前同事和共犯
Your former coworker and accomplice,
Xavier Blackburn
Xavier Blackburn?
他正被NCIS拘留
He's in NCIS custody.
以破紀錄的時間就把你供出來了
Gave you up in record time.
別...別聽他們的
Do... do not listen to them.
這是個圈套
This is a setup.
Kinneman是個軍事承包商
Kinneman's a military contractor.
他為什麼要幫塔利班呢
Why would he be helping the Taliban?
簡單的經濟學
Simple economics.
美軍從喀布爾撤軍
U.S. forces pull out of Kabul,
他得以從中謀利的國防合同也就消失了
的his lucrative defense contracts disappear.
如果這個區域的敵軍襲擊增加
If enemy attacks increase in the area,
美軍就會加強部署
U.S. military strengthens their presence,
你的資金也就得到了保障
securing your funding.
所以你開始給Atwa傳遞
So you started passing Intel to Atwa
可以用來襲擊那幾個車隊的情報
on certain convoys to attack.
但是Voit上尉開始打探信息
But Captain Voit started digging around,
而你必須終結這件事
and you had to put an end to it.
所以你讓Atwa襲擊Voit的車隊
Then you had Atwa strike Voit's convoy.
然後你在Atwa供出你之前射殺了他
Then you shot Atwa before he could give you up.
對於一個受過高等狙擊訓練的人
Easy target for someone
比如你而言 這個目標太簡單了
with advanced sniper training, such as yourself.
得了 Kinneman
Come on, Kinneman,
這些人理應知道的
these guys deserve to know.
那些陸戰隊員的性命值多少錢呢
How much were those Marines' lives worth, huh?
五百萬嗎 還是一千萬
Five million? Ten?
這跟錢無關
It wasn't about money.
你開玩笑嗎 如果軍隊撤出
Are you kidding me?! If the military withdraws
塔利班再次控制這片區域
and the Taliban takes control of this area again,
那我們過去15年裏打的仗都是為了什麼
then what were the last 15 years of fighting even for?
嘿 14個人因你而死
Hey, 14 people are dead because of you.
你跟Atwa那樣的恐怖分子沒什麼兩樣
You're as much a terrorist as anyone like Atwa.
把你的雙手放在身後
Put your hands behind your back.
嘿 醫生 我需要你在這個遺體轉運書上
Hey, Doctor, I need your signature
簽字
on this body transfer.
-發生了什麼 -我正在恰當地
- What's going on? - I am properly
展示你的藝術作品
displaying your artwork.
這些都應當被展示出來並接受贊賞
All these should be shown and admired.
我不敢相信你這麼做了
I can't believe that you did this.
我很感動
I am touched.
哦 把這當做分別禮物吧
Oh, consider it a parting gift.
分別禮物 你要去哪裏嗎
Parting gift? You going somewhere?
是的
Indeed I am.
你可以把這當成環球曆險
You can call it a globetrotting adventure.
但是你剛回來
But you just got back.
你在過去的一年裏 已經證明自己完全能夠勝任
You have proven yourself more than capable
這裏的工作 Palmer醫生
in the last year, Dr. Palmer.
我完全相信你會在我離開的時間裏
I have no doubt that you'll continue
繼續守住這個堡壘
to hold the fort while I'm gone.
沒問題 但是你會回來的 對吧
Sure, but you will be back, right?
當然
Of course.
當我在新的一年裏回來的時候
And when I return in the new year,
我會有更多的故事可以講給你聽
I shall have many more stories to relate.
哦 那真是太棒了
Well, that's great.
你曆險的第一站是哪裏呢
What's the first stop on your vacation gonna be?
比較 呃 有異國情調的地方嗎
Something, uh, exotic?
也許是金字塔 中國長城
Maybe the pyramids, Great Wall of China?
坦桑尼亞的塞倫蓋蒂平原
The Serengeti?
拉什莫爾山
【注：在美國南達科他州西部，山上懸崖鑿有華盛頓、傑弗遜 、林肯、老羅斯福巨型頭像】
Mount Rushmore.
南達科他州 在冬天裏
South Dakota. In the middle of winter.
嗯
Mm.
你是那麼與眾不同 醫生
You are one in a million, Doctor.
沒錯
True.
謝謝你的配合 上校
Thank you for your cooperation, Colonel.
你知道 這個護送任務是重中之重
You know, this escort mission has top priority.
我應該感謝你 Gibbs
I should be the one thanking you, Gibbs.
那些應該為Voit上尉的死負責的人
Those responsible for Captain Voit's death
接受了正義的審判
have been brought to justice.
我只希望每個戰士犧牲的時候都能得到正義的守護
I only wish that could happen for every fallen service member.
上尉的葬禮是在什麼時候
What time is the captain's funeral?
明天上午9點
0900 hours tomorrow.
新澤西州 Strathmere市
Strathmere, New Jersey.
開車去要大概五小時 需要導航員嗎
That's about a five-hour drive. Looking for a navigator?
你的出差包准備好了嗎 軍士長
You have your go-bag, Gunny?
已經打好包了 就在車裏
Already packed. It's in the car.
有人陪著當然好啊
Company would be nice.
我知道Voit會很感激
I know Voit would appreciate having
有另一個陸戰隊員能去送她
another Marine there to see her off.
這是我的榮幸
My honor.
你會非常喜歡她的 GIbbs
You would have really liked her, Gibbs.
她一直都非常堅定
She was as determined as they come.
從未退縮過
Never backed down from a fight.
我們走吧
Shall we?
好
Yeah.
安息吧 陸戰隊員
Rest easy, Marine.
我們來守護你
We got the watch.
翻譯：湯湯 柒九一九 二噁英 小飛
校對： 二噁英 小飛
主校：Vincent
分配：雞血
== sync, corrected by elderman == @elder_man